<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Basics on Dkron - Distributed job scheduling system</title>
    <link>/basics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basics on Dkron - Distributed job scheduling system</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>/basics/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/basics/installation/</guid>
      <description>Running the binary Download the packaged archive for your platform from the downloads page and extract the package to a shared location in your drive, like /opt/local/bin.
Run Dkron with default setting: dkron agent --server
Navigate to http://localhost:8080
By default dkron will start with a file based, embedded KV store called BoltDB, it is functional for a single node demo but does not offers clustering or HA.
 Installing the package Debian repo APT repository:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>/basics/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/basics/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Dkron nodes can work in two modes, agents or servers.
A Dkron agent is a cluster member that can handle job executions, run your scripts and return the resulting output to the server.
A Dkron server is also a cluster member that send job execution queries to agents or other servers, so servers can execute jobs too.
The main distinction is that servers order job executions, can be used to schedule jobs, handles data storage and participate on leader election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>/basics/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/basics/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Settings for dkron can be specified in three ways: Using a config/dkron.json config file, using env variables starting with DKRON_ or using command line arguments.
Command line options  --node-name - Name of the node, must be unique in the cluster. By default this is the hostname of the machine.
 --bind-addr - The address that dkron will bind to for communication with other dkron nodes. By default this is &amp;ldquo;0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>