<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Basics on Dkron - Cloud native job scheduling system</title>
    <link>/basics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basics on Dkron - Cloud native job scheduling system</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>/basics/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/basics/installation/</guid>
      <description>Running the binary Download the packaged archive for your platform from the downloads page and extract the package to a shared location in your drive, like /opt/local/bin.
Run Dkron with default setting: dkron agent --server --bootstrap-expect=1
Navigate to http://localhost:8080/ui
Installing the package Debian repo APT repository:
deb [trusted=yes] https://repo.distrib.works/apt/ / Then install: sudo apt-get install dkron
YUM repo YUM repository:
[dkron] name=Dkron Pro Private Repo baseurl=https://repo.distrib.works/yum/ enabled=1 gpgcheck=0 Then install: sudo yum install dkron</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>/basics/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/basics/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Dkron nodes can work in two modes, agents or servers.
A Dkron agent is a cluster member that can handle job executions, run your scripts and return the resulting output to the server.
A Dkron server is also a cluster member that send job execution queries to agents or other servers, so servers can execute jobs too.
The main distinction is that servers order job executions, can be used to schedule jobs, handles data storage and participate on leader election.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>/basics/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/basics/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Configuration sources Settings can be specified in three ways (in order of precedence):
 Command line arguments. Environment variables starting with DKRON_ dkron.yml config file  Note: Dkron sends anonymous usage data to a server with the purpose of elaborating usage statistics, if you want to disable statistics collection, you can disable it in the dkron config file or in the command line using --disable-usage-stats parameter Config file location Config file will be loaded from the following paths:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>