<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CLI on Dkron - Distributed job scheduling system</title>
    <link>/v2.0/cli/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CLI on Dkron - Distributed job scheduling system</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/v2.0/cli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>dkron</title>
      <link>/cli/dkron/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cli/dkron/</guid>
      <description>dkron Open source distributed job scheduling system
Synopsis Dkron is a system service that runs scheduled jobs at given intervals or times, just like the cron unix service but distributed in several machines in a cluster. If a machine fails (the leader), a follower will take over and keep running the scheduled jobs without human intervention.
Options  --config string config file path -h, --help help for dkron SEE ALSO  dkron agent	- Start a dkron agent dkron doc	- Generate Markdown documentation for the Dkron CLI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dkron agent</title>
      <link>/cli/dkron_agent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cli/dkron_agent/</guid>
      <description>dkron agent Start a dkron agent
Synopsis Start a dkron agent that schedules jobs, listens for executions and runs executors. It also runs a web UI.
dkron agent [flags] Options  --advertise-addr string Address used to advertise to other nodes in the cluster. By default, the bind address is advertised. The value supports go-sockaddr/template format. --advertise-rpc-port int Use the value of rpc-port by default --bind-addr string Specifies which address the agent should bind to for network services, including the internal gossip protocol and RPC mechanism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dkron doc</title>
      <link>/cli/dkron_doc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cli/dkron_doc/</guid>
      <description>dkron doc Generate Markdown documentation for the Dkron CLI.
Synopsis Generate Markdown documentation for the Dkron CLI. This command is, mostly, used to create up-to-date documentation of Dkron&amp;rsquo;s command-line interface for http://dkron.io/. It creates one Markdown file per command with front matter suitable for rendering in Hugo.
dkron doc [flags] Options  --dir string the directory to write the doc. (default &amp;quot;/tmp/dkrondoc/&amp;quot;) -h, --help help for doc Options inherited from parent commands  --config string config file path SEE ALSO  dkron	- Open source distributed job scheduling system  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 10-Oct-2019 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dkron keygen</title>
      <link>/cli/dkron_keygen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cli/dkron_keygen/</guid>
      <description>dkron keygen Generates a new encryption key
Synopsis Generates a new encryption key that can be used to configure the agent to encrypt traffic. The output of this command is already in the proper format that the agent expects.
dkron keygen [flags] Options  -h, --help help for keygen Options inherited from parent commands  --config string config file path SEE ALSO  dkron	- Open source distributed job scheduling system  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 10-Oct-2019 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dkron leave</title>
      <link>/cli/dkron_leave/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cli/dkron_leave/</guid>
      <description>dkron leave Force an agent to leave the cluster
Synopsis Stop stops an agent, if the agent is a server and is running for election stop running for election, if this server was the leader this will force the cluster to elect a new leader and start a new scheduler.
dkron leave [flags] Options  -h, --help help for leave --rpc-addr string gRPC address of the agent (default &amp;quot;127.0.0.1:6868&amp;quot;) Options inherited from parent commands  --config string config file path SEE ALSO  dkron	- Open source distributed job scheduling system  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 10-Oct-2019 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dkron raft</title>
      <link>/cli/dkron_raft/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cli/dkron_raft/</guid>
      <description>dkron raft Command to perform some raft operations
Synopsis Command to perform some raft operations
Options  -h, --help help for raft --rpc-addr string gRPC address of the agent (default &amp;quot;127.0.0.1:6868&amp;quot;) Options inherited from parent commands  --config string config file path SEE ALSO  dkron	- Open source distributed job scheduling system dkron raft list-peers	- Command to list raft peers dkron raft remove-peer	- Command to list raft peers  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 10-Oct-2019 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dkron raft list-peers</title>
      <link>/cli/dkron_raft_list-peers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cli/dkron_raft_list-peers/</guid>
      <description>dkron raft list-peers Command to list raft peers
Synopsis Command to list raft peers
dkron raft list-peers [flags] Options  -h, --help help for list-peers Options inherited from parent commands  --config string config file path --rpc-addr string gRPC address of the agent (default &amp;quot;127.0.0.1:6868&amp;quot;) SEE ALSO  dkron raft	- Command to perform some raft operations  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 10-Oct-2019 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dkron raft remove-peer</title>
      <link>/cli/dkron_raft_remove-peer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cli/dkron_raft_remove-peer/</guid>
      <description>dkron raft remove-peer Command to list raft peers
Synopsis Command to list raft peers
dkron raft remove-peer [flags] Options  -h, --help help for remove-peer --peer-id string Remove a Dkron server with the given ID from the Raft configuration. Options inherited from parent commands  --config string config file path --rpc-addr string gRPC address of the agent (default &amp;quot;127.0.0.1:6868&amp;quot;) SEE ALSO  dkron raft	- Command to perform some raft operations  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 10-Oct-2019 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dkron version</title>
      <link>/cli/dkron_version/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cli/dkron_version/</guid>
      <description>dkron version Show version
Synopsis Show the version
dkron version [flags] Options  -h, --help help for version Options inherited from parent commands  --config string config file path SEE ALSO  dkron	- Open source distributed job scheduling system  Auto generated by spf13/cobra on 10-Oct-2019 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>